{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
      {
          "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=",
          "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
          "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
          "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGRpZ2l0YWwgZGlzdHJpYnV0aW9uIHBsYXRmb3JtIFN0ZWFtPw==",
          "correct_answer": "VmFsdmU=",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "UGl4ZWx0YWlsIEdhbWVz",
              "VWJpc29mdA==",
              "RWxlY3Ryb25pYyBBcnRz"
          ]
      },
      {
          "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=",
          "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
          "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
          "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBleHBlbnNpdmUgd2VhcG9uIGluIENvdW50ZXItU3RyaWtlOiBHbG9iYWwgT2ZmZW5zaXZlPw==",
          "correct_answer": "U2Nhci0yMC9HM1NHMQ==",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "TTRBMQ==",
              "QVdQ",
              "UjggUmV2b2x2ZXI="
          ]
      },
      {
          "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=",
          "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
          "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
          "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGNhbmNlbGxlZCBzZXF1ZWwgb2YgVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcz8=",
          "correct_answer": "VGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyOiBCcm90aGVyaG9vZCBvZiBBcm1z",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "VGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyOiBEZXNlcnQgTWVyY2VuYXJpZXM=",
              "VGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyOiBPcGVyYXRpb24gR2VhciBHcmluZGVy",
              "VGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyOiBSZXR1cm4gdG8gQ2xhc3NpYw=="
          ]
      },
      {
          "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=",
          "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
          "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
          "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBoZWFsaW5nIGl0ZW0gaW4gRGFyayBTb3Vscz8=",
          "correct_answer": "RXN0dXMgRmxhc2s=",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "SGVhbHRoIFBvdGlvbg==",
              "T3JhbmdlIEp1aWNl",
              "QXNoZW4gRmxhc2s="
          ]
      },
      {
          "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=",
          "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
          "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
          "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgbWFpbiBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gIkdyYW5kIFRoZWZ0IEF1dG8gViI/",
          "correct_answer": "TGFtYXI=",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "VHJldm9y",
              "TWljaGFlbA==",
              "RnJhbmtsaW4="
          ]
      },
      {
          "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=",
          "type": "Ym9vbGVhbg==",
          "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
          "question": "SW4gS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMgdGhlIFBhb3B1IGZydWl0IGlzIHNhaWQgdG8gaW50ZXJ0d2luZSB0aGUgZGVzdGluaWVzIGZvciB0d28gcGVvcGxlIGZvcmV2ZXIu",
          "correct_answer": "VHJ1ZQ==",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "RmFsc2U="
          ]
      },
      {
          "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=",
          "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
          "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
          "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgJ1BvcnRhbCAyJyByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
          "correct_answer": "MjAxMQ==",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "MjAxNA==",
              "MjAwOQ==",
              "MjAwNw=="
          ]
      },
      {
          "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=",
          "type": "Ym9vbGVhbg==",
          "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
          "question": "RGV1cyBFeCAoMjAwMCkgZG9lcyBub3QgZmVhdHVyZSB0aGUgV29ybGQgVHJhZGUgQ2VudGVyIGJlY2F1c2UgaXQgd2FzIGRlc3Ryb3llZCBieSB0ZXJyb3Jpc3QgYXR0YWNrcyBhY2NvcmRpbmcgdG8gdGhlIGdhbWUncyBwbG90Lg==",
          "correct_answer": "VHJ1ZQ==",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "RmFsc2U="
          ]
      },
      {
          "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=",
          "type": "Ym9vbGVhbg==",
          "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
          "question": "SW4gU3BsYXRvb24sIHRoZSBTcXVpZCBTaXN0ZXJzIGFyZSBuYW1lZCBUYWtvIGFuZCBZYWtpLg==",
          "correct_answer": "RmFsc2U=",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "VHJ1ZQ=="
          ]
      },
      {
          "category": "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=",
          "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
          "difficulty": "ZWFzeQ==",
          "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBhIGNsYXNzIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lICJIZWFydGhzdG9uZSI/",
          "correct_answer": "UHJpZXN0",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "U2FnZQ==",
              "Q2xlcmlj",
              "TW9uaw=="
          ]
      }
  ]
}